A Finding Aid to the Constance Glenn Papers, 1960s-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Constance Glenn papers
1960s-2014
Archives of American Art
Glenn, Constance, 1933-
AAA.glencons
Archival Resource Key
17.1 Linear feet
6.88 Gigabytes
The papers of writer, art historian, and curator Constance Glenn measure 17.1 linear feet and 6.88 GB and date from the 1960s to 2014. The material documents Glenn's career through correspondence, writings, book project files, exhibition documentation, professional records, research files, printed and digital material, and some photographs. Also well documented is Glenn's tenure as Museum Director and educator at California State University, Long Beach.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center. Researchers interested in accessing born-digital records or audiovisual recordings in this collection must use access copies. Contact References Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated by Constance Glenn in 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Constance Glenn (1933-) is an art historian, writer, and curator in California. Glenn was the founding director of the University Art Museum at California State University, Long Beach. She received her Bachelor of Fine Art from the University of Kansas in 1955, and completed her Masters of Arts in Fine Art from California State University as she simultaneously founded the University Art Museum at CSULB in 1973. During her career at CSULB, the University Art Museum grew from a small gallery-sized exhibition space to a nationally-celebrated contemporary art museum. Glenn also founded the Graduate Certificate Program in Museum Studies at CSULB, and taught art history and museum studies courses at the university.
Exhibitions curated by Glenn include Frances Benjamin Johnson: Women of Status and Station (1979); Eric Fischl: Scenes Before the Eye (1986-1987); James Rosenquist: Time Dust/The Complete Graphics (1962-1992); The Great America Pop Art Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997); and Candida Hofer: Architecture of Absence (2004). In addition, Glenn served as a consulting curator for A Happening Place (2003), curated by Cheryl Harper for the Gershman Y in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
As an art historian and writer, Glenn participated in lectures and panel discussions as well as published essays, articles, and books. Glenn was an editor and feature writer for Antiques & Fine Art, Angeles Magazine, and Architectural Digest; contributed biographical articles to the Dictionary of Art and Encyclopedia Americana; and was involved with professional associations such as the J. Paul Getty Trust Fund for the Visual Arts, Art/LA, Association of Art Museum Directors, and the Archives of American Art.
Glenn was married to art dealer Jack Glenn (1933-2014).
Scope and Contents
The papers of writer, art historian, curator and museum director Constance Glenn measure 17.1 linear feet and 6.88 GB and date from the 1960s to 2014. The papers consist of material related to Glenn's writings and book projects, curated exhibitions, professional associations, research, involvement with California State University, Long Beach, and printed and digital material. Exhibition openings, panel discussions, and interviews are present in the format of sound and video recordings. Also included are correspondence, photographs, and a small series related to Glenn's interest and experience in art collecting, including price lists, inventories, and provenance records.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged as 11 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1983-1993 (Box 1, 7 folders, ER01; 0.758 GB)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1972-2014 (Box 1-2, 0.8 linear feet)
Series 3: Writings, 1981-2011 (Box 2-4, 2 linear feet)
Series 4: Book Projects, 1984-1999 (Box 4-6, 2.5 linear feet)
Series 5: Artist Files, 1976-2005 (Box 6-7, 1 linear feet, ER02-ER05; 2.54 GB)
Series 6: Exhibition Files, 1979-2003 (Box 7-10, 2.1 linear feet, ER06-ER07; 3.53 GB)
Series 7: Professional Files, 1979-2007 (Box 11-12, 1.3 linear feet)
Series 8: California State University, Long Beach, Files, 1975-2001 (Box 12-13, 1.8 linear feet, ER08; 0.051 GB)
Series 9: Art Inventory and Sales Records, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 13-14, 1 linear feet)
Series 10: Printed Material, 1960s-2014 (Box 14-15, 1.8 linear feet)
Series 11: Photographs, circa 1960s-2000s (Box 16-17, 2 linear feet)
Interviews; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Women authors; Art museum curators -- California; Authors -- California; Art historians -- California; California State University, Long Beach
- Biographical Material, 1983-1993; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 7 Folders Box 1; 0.758 Gigabytes ER01
  Scope and Contents
  Biographical Files include address and contact lists, audiovisual and digital material, and a file regarding the education of Constance Glenn's son, Chris.
  - Address and Contact List, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Profiles, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chris Glenn Educational Material, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Phone Contact Information, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CBS Sunday Morning, 1993 November 21; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Recording, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "1968", Digital Video Recording, 2000s; Archival Resource Key; 0.758 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER01)
- Correspondence, 1972-2014; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; .8 Linear feet Box 1-2
  Correspondence includes letters sent and received by Constance Glenn of a predominantly professional nature. Her correspondents include artists, colleagues in the museum world, and a few professional organizations.
  - Friedman, Ken, 1972-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Killian, Tom, 1998-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Livingston, Marco, 1987-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
  - McGraw, DeLoss, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Roy Lichtenstein Foundation, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Wesselman, Tom, 1999, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1979-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
  - General Correspondence, 1990-2014, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
- Writings, 1981-2011; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 2 Linear feet Box 2-4
  Writings include drafts, research, and some correspondence related to essays, articles, and book chapters authored by Constance Glenn. Found here are files regarding her writing and editing for Architectural Digest, Angeles Magazine, The Dictionary of Art, Encyclopedia Americana, along with her contributions to chapters of books on American pop art. Also included in this series are notes and drafts of essays, some of which are titled. Of note are sound recordings of interviews with individuals for Architectural Digest, including artists Richard Diebenkorn and Nathan Oliveira.
  - Architectural Digest, Papers, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Digest, Richard Diebenkorn, 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 2, Folder 7)
    File also contains correspondence, notes, and other papers.
  - Architectural Digest, Nathan Oliveira, circa 1983; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Architectural Digest, Armand Hammer, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Architectural Digest, Wayne Thiebaud, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Angeles Magazine, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11-14)
  - The Dictionary of Art, Papers and Correspondence, 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Dictionary of Art, Research, circa 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Dictionary of Art, Completed Entries, circa 1987-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - The Dictionary of Art, Online Version, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Art and Artists, Roy Lichtenstein, circa 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pop Art (1991), Catalog Essayist, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3-8)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, Correspondence and Drafts, circa 1994-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9-11)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, Articles, circa 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Biographical Articles, circa 1998-2000, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Encyclopedia of 20th Century Photography, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Parket Series with Contemporary Artists, James Rosenquist, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, Tom Wesselmann Catalog Essayist, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - "Discovering the Mathews: The California Decorative Style", circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Notes, The Relationship Between Art and Architecture, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Tom Wesselman and Drawing", circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Los Angeles Art History, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Pop Art: An American Memoir", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - William Wendt in Context, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Proposed Articles, Correspondence and Drafts, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - California Art History Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Research Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographic Notecards, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Book Projects, 1984-1999; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 2.5 Linear feet Box 4-6
  Arrangement
  There is one unidentified audio cassette that was discovered upon processing. It is kept with Jim Dine's book project files in its original order.
  Book Projects consists of correspondence, research files, book agreements, manuscripts, and photographs mostly documenting Constance Glenn's involvement with the Harry N. Abrams Inc. artists' sketchbook series. Co-authored by Jack Glenn, Constance's husband, the Glenns wrote the text and edited the published sketchbooks of Jim Dine, Roy Lichtenstein, Lucas Samaras, Wayne Thiebaud, and Robert Motherwell. Files also exist on other artists who were part of this series, but ultimately did not publish their sketchbooks at this time. These artists include Eric Fischl, Richard Diebenkorn, and Ellsworth Kelly.
  Also included is a subgroup of proposed books consisting of correspondence, research material, writings, and some book agreements.
  - Harry Abrams Inc., Papers and Agreements, 1984-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Harry Abrams Inc., Legal Papers, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Agreements, 1983-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Correspondence, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Letters of Permission, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Drafts, circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10-14)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Sketchbook Copies, circa 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Research, 1959-1984, circa 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Research, 1959-1984, circa 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Research and Lists, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Research, Exhibition and Collection Printed Material, circa 1974-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Interview Transcripts, circa 1974-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6-11)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), BBC, Jim Dine Seeing Through Drawing, circa 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), New York, 1979 January 30; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Recording, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 5, Folder 14-16)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Boston MFA, 1983 March 23; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), California State University Long Beach, 1983 July 19; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Jim Dine: Free Artist, Self Portrait of the Contemporary Painter, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Unidentified, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jim Dine Drawings (1985), Book Publicity, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Roy Lichtenstein: Landscape Sketches (1986), Papers, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Roy Lichtenstein: Landscape Sketches (1986), Interview, 1985 August 28; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (microcassette) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lucas Samaras: Doodles, Sketches and Plans (1986), Agreements, Correspondence, Writings, and Research, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lucas Samaras: Doodles, Sketches and Plans (1986), Samaras on Sketchbooks, 1985 November 6; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassettes (microcassette) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Wayne Thiebaud: Private Drawings (1987), Papers, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Wayne Thiebaud: Private Drawings (1987), Thiebaud on Sketchbooks, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Robert Motherwell: The Dedalus Sketches (1988), Research, circa 1983-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Robert Motherwell: The Dedalus Sketches (1988), Provincetown Sketchbook, 1985 September 1; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassettes (microcassette) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sketchbooks, David Hockney, Correspondence and Writings, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sketchbooks, Eric Fischl, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sketchbooks, Richard Diebenkorn, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sketchbooks, Ellsworth Kelly, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Book Projects, Archival Resource Key
    - Collectors Book, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Los Angeles: Artful Eating, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - DeLoss McGraw and W.D. Snodgrass, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Texas Book Ideas, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - D.H. Lawrence: Among Many Talents, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Abrams Publishing, Lucas Samaras Art "Never Seen" Book Idea, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Abrams Publishing, L'Affaire La Belle, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - National Museum of American Art and Abrams Publishing Book, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Perfume Book, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Bryan Hunt, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Frances Benjamin Johnson, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Wayne Thiebaud, Correspondence and Research, 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
    - Phaidon Press, Pop Art, 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Book Ideas, Constance Glenn and Laurie Glenn Buckle, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Words and Pictures: Illustrated by Contemporary Artists, 1965-1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Artist Files, 1976-2005; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Box 6-7; 2.54 Gigabytes ER02-ER05
  Artists Files include sound and video recordings, interview transcripts, and some papers related to artists who were of interest to Constance Glenn.
  Researchers should note that additional information on some of the artists in this series may be found in Series 4: Book Projects and Series 6: Exhibition Files.
  - Jo Ann Callis, Digital Presentation and Photographs, 2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.086 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER02)
  - Jim Elliot Interview, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassettes (microcassette) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - David Hockney, Seeing Through Drawing, circa 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - David Hockney: The Magic Flute, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - David Hockney, "A Day on the Grand Canal with the Emperor of China", 1989; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - David Hockney Sets, Puccini's "Turandot" with Eva Marton, 1993; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Kasten Interview, 1981; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Contains digital materials, see ER02 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Kasten Interview (1981), Digital Audio Recording, 2014; Archival Resource Key; 0.203 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER03)
  - Roy Lichtenstein, Portrait of an Artist, 2000; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Rosenquist," CBS Sunday Morning, 1986; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - James Rosenquist, "Printers Impressions", 1990; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - James Rosenquist, Russian Film, 1993; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - James Rosenquist, Interview Transcript, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Wayne Thiebaud, Interview Questions, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Wayne Thiebaud Panel Discussion, Laguna Art Museum, Digital Video Recording, 2013 October 12; Archival Resource Key; 2.21 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER04)
  - "Reaching Out: Ken Tyler, Master Printer", 1967; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel 16mm (Box FC 18)
  - "Reaching Out: Ken Tyler, Master Printer", 1976; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tom Wesselman, Papers, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key; Contains digital materials, see ER05 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Tom Wesselman, Artwork, Digital Photographs, 2001-2005; Archival Resource Key; 0.039 Gigabytes 222 computer files (Folder ER05)
  - Artist Panel Discussion, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Exhibition Files, 1979-2003; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 2.1 Linear feet Box 7-10; 3.53 Gigabytes ER06-ER07
  Exhibition files document Constance Glenn's curation of exhibitions both at the University Art Museum where she served as director and curator and elsewhere as a consulting curator. Included are planning documents, correspondence, inventories, loan forms, research files, condition reports, photographs, printed material, and some video and sound recordings.
  Researchers should note that some information on the artists in this series, especially that which date after Glenn's exhibitions, may be found in Series 5: Artist Files.
  - Frances Benjamin Johnson: Women of Class and Station (1979), Writings and Papers, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Frances Benjamin Johnson: Women of Class and Station (1979), Research, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Frances Benjamin Johnson, Images and Notes, circa 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Frances Benjamin Johnson, Exhibition Book, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Frances Benjamin Johnson, Bibliographic File, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tom Wesselman: The Early Years Collages, 1959-1962 (1974-1975), Papers, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Centric 13: Susan Rothberg Works on Paper (1985), Writings, circa 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Eric Fischl: Scenes Before the Eye (1986-1987), Research and Notes, 1965-1986, 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Eric Fischl: Scenes Before the Eye (1986-1987), Catalog Draft, circa 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eric Fischl, Interview Transcript, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Eric Fischl; Weinberg, undated; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound cassettes (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Writings and Lists, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Raisonne, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Notes, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Catalog Draft, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15-17)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Printed Material and Artist Samples, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - James Rosenquist: Time Dust, The Complete Graphics, 1962-1992 (1993), Talk with Rosenquist, Constance Glenn, and Ken Tyler, Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Requiem for a Paperweight (1994), 1995; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 8, Folder 20)
    File also includes a letter from photographer Arthur Tress.
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Correspondence, circa 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Checklists, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Notes, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Research, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5-13)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Research, The Pop Image: Prints and Mulitples (1994) at Marlborough Gallery, Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Catalog Papers, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Installation Cards, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Damaged Bob Watts Art, 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Printed Material and Ephemera, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Printed Material and Ephemera, 1997-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Great American Pop Store: Multiples of the Sixties (1997), Photographs, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Artist's Proofs: Photographs by Sidney Felsen (1999), Papers, 1999-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Double Vision: Photographs from the Strauss Collection (2001), Notes, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Tom Wesselmann: The Intimate Images (2003), Papers, 2002-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)